oyez.org 2014-02-09

# The Oyez Project at Chicago-Kent - Privacy Policy | The Oyez Project at IIT Chicago-Kent College of Law

The Oyez Project at Chicago-Kent (Oyez) respects your privacy. This privacy policy explains how Oyez collects, uses and safeguards information on [www.oyez.org](http://www.oyez.org/ "www.oyez.org"), and any other websites operated by Oyez such as oyeztoday.org and [www.pocketjustice.com](http://www.pocketjustice.com/ "www.pocketjustice.com"). This privacy policy applies only to information collected by Oyez and its related websites.

## Changes to the Privacy Policy

Our privacy policy is likely to change from time to time simply to keep abreast of changes in technology. We reserve the right to amend our policy at any time, for any reason. The date of the last revision to our policy will be indicated by the "Last updated" date at the bottom of this page.

If you have questions about our privacy policy, please email us at [privacy@oyez.org](mailto:privacy@oyez.org).

## What information we collect and how we use it

We use advertising networks to help present advertisements on Oyez sites. These advertising networks use "cookies" to help present, better target, and measure the effectiveness of their advertisements, using data gathered over time and across their networks to determine the characteristics and preferences of their audience. (A "cookie" is a packet of data sent by an Internet server to a browser, which is returned by the browser each time it subsequently accesses the same server; it is used to track the user's access to the server.)

We may share certain aggregate and non-personally-identifiable information about our users in order to help them deliver more relevant advertisements through their ad networks. The Bizographic Targeting Network (Bizo) is one such network in which we participate. If you wish to ‘opt out’ of the targeted advertising delivered by Bizo, please click <http://www.bizo.com/business_audience/opt_out> to visit the Bizo opt out page. Or, you may opt out of multiple ad-targeting cookies, including Bizo, via that National Advertising Initiative opt-out page: [http://www.bizo.com/business_audience/opt_out](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

## What information we do not collect

We do not collect personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, phone number and e-mail address.

## Linking to other Internet sites

You should be aware that other Internet sites that are linked from Oyez or its related sites may contain privacy provisions that differ from the provisions of the Oyez privacy policy. To ensure your privacy is protected, we recommend that you review the privacy statements of other Internet sites you visit.

Last updated July 11, 2011
